Pick a card.
选一张
All right. Now,memorize it.
好 记住花色号码
-You got it? -Oh, yes.
好了没？ 好了
Is that your card?
是这张吗？
Yes.
就是这张
-Hey,guys. -Hi there!
大家好
Guess what. Ben is gonna be in a TV commercial.
你们猜怎么着？ 班要上电视拍广告了
What are you talking about?
你们在说什么？
It's not for sure,but...
还没有定案
...we met this guy in the park who thought Ben was cute.
不过我们在公园里遇到一个人 他觉得班很可爱
You know,which he is. He gave us his card...
这也是事实啦 那个人留了张名片
...and told us to bring him for this commercial he's auditioning.
要我带班去参加广告试镜
This guy's the biggest commercial casting director in town!
这个人是本地最大的选角导演
Ben takes one lousy walk in the park and gets an audition?
班去公园随便散个步 就有试镜自动送上门！
I mean, way to go, Ben!
我是说，班，真有你的
I've been in that park a million times and no one's offered me an audition.
那个公园我都去烂了 从来没人主动找我去试镜
It's crazy. We were pushing Ben on the swings
我知道，真的很神奇 我们只是在陪班玩荡秋千…
I'm always on the swings!
我每次都在玩荡秋千啊
What am I doing wrong?
我是哪里做错了？
That.
就是那里
The One Where Rachel Smokes
本集播出：“打入抽烟圈”
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
-Gotta go. Wish me luck. -Good luck.
我要出门了，祝我好运
Since you work at Ralph Lauren, can you get me some shirts?
瑞秋，既然你在拉夫罗伦工作 能不能带几件马球衫回来？
I don't know if I'd feel comfortable stealing on my very first day.
第一天上班就偷公司东西 我可能下不了手喔
Unwilling to steal from work.
不愿意慷公司之慨
Interesting.
有意思了
If anybody gets free stuff, it's me.
就算有人能拿免费的 那也非我莫属
Okay,guys,way to wish me luck.
好了，各位，祝我好运吧
Go get 'em!
祝你好运，给他们好看
Let's discuss Rachel's birthday.
好，来讨论帮瑞秋庆生的事
I say we throw a surprise party this weekend.
我建议在周末办惊喜派对
But her birthday's not for another month.
可是一个月后才是她生日啊
If we throw her party on her birthday, it's not a surprise.
是没错，但在生日当天开派对 那就不惊喜啦
Great! We can have a dinner party and just invite her close friends.
我觉得这主意不错 我们办个晚餐派对 邀请好朋友过来
Ross! We're having a surprise party for Rachel.
罗斯！ 我们要帮瑞秋办惊喜派对咯
Done.
搞定
Great. Wanna do it together?
好，那你要一起来吗？
I'd love to do it together!
乐意之至
They're gonna do it together.
她们要一起来耶
That's my girlfriend.
兄弟，那位可是我女友
So I gotta shut it down now?
所以我就得闭嘴？
I gotta go. I'm picking up Ben...
好，我得走了 我要接班...
...and then we're off to the big audition.
...去参加大试镜
It's gonna be weird seeing some actor pretending to be Ben's dad.
看到有演员假装是班的父亲 那种感觉一定很怪
Weirder than seeing his two moms make out?
是啊 怪过看班的两个妈妈温存？
Dad? There's a dad in the commercial?
爸爸？广告里面有爸爸？
Yeah. The dad and Ben eat soup and pretend to enjoy it.
是啊，班和爸爸喝汤 演得很陶醉的样子
Maybe I'll go with you and audition as the dad.
或许我可以跟你们一起去 搞不好能试镜演那个爸爸
Who better to play Ben's father than his godfather?
说到扮演班的爸爸 由我这教父上场更最适合了
-You're not his godfather. -What?
你不是班的教父 什么？
Are you kidding?
你在开玩笑吧？
Of course I am.
当然是啊
-Okay, let's go, godfather. -All right!
我们走吧，教父 好耶
They're gonna let me audition!
我获选了，他们让我试镜
Really? That's great!
真的？太棒了
One of the casting ladies has actually seen me in a play.
有个女的看过我演舞台剧
So I steered clear of her.
所以我离她离得远远的
And the other one,I know from....
另一个我也认识
Well,you know.
原因你也知道…
-That kid looks familiar. -Oh,yeah.
那个孩子看起来很眼熟 是啊
He's done tons of commercials. I've seen him in Sugar Smacks, PlayStation...
他拍过一堆广告 有糖果广告、新力PS游戏机
...and that one for the phone company.
还帮电话公司拍过广告
He was so good,he convinced me to switch phone companies.
他演得实在是太好了 我索性跟着换了电话公司
Chandler was mad.
钱德因此还气得半死
He's not gonna get this one. Ben is way cuter than that kid.
不过他这次休想拿到这角色 因为班比他可爱多了
I mean, look at him.
看就知道，宝贝，看看你
That's great.
很好
Wouldn't it be great if I got to play Ben's dad?
不过若我能演班的爸爸 这样是不是很棒？
You look nothing like Ben.
乔伊，你跟班一点都不像
I look more like him than you do.
比你跟他像多了
I really don't know you well enough for you to do that.
我跟你还不熟 哪里生得出小孩？
So it's down to these two. Nancy,I know you like this one.
现在是最后的二选一 南茜，我知道你喜欢这一个
I think I agree. Rachel,what do you think?
我也有同感 瑞秋，你觉得呢？
Well, that one is pretty...
那个是很漂亮
...but I just love this fabric.
但我超爱这个的质料
Sorry.
抱歉了
Don't be. Part of your job is to give your opinions.
不用抱歉 提供意见是你的职责之一
Then I take credit for them. I'm kidding!
功劳归我，开玩笑的
She is kidding. But don't ever disagree with her again.
她这次是在开玩笑 但下次可别跟她意见相左
Okay,now I'm kidding!
这次换我在开玩笑
What a fun office.
这个办公室真有趣
I don't know which one. But I do know I need a cigarette.
我不知道要选哪一个 不过先来根烟倒是真的
Let's take a break, go outside and sort this out when we return.
不如我们出去休息一下 等回来之后再解决？
-You smoke? -No.
你抽烟吗？ 不抽
My dad's a doctor. And he would always tell me horror stories....
不抽，我爸是医生 老跟我说些恐怖的故事…
About ghosts and goblins...
说那些鬼神精灵的…
...who totally supported the princess' right to smoke.
完全赞同公主抽烟
And then they came back from smoking and they'd made all of the decisions.
她们在抽烟的时候 就背着我做出了决定
-That's not fair. -I know.
这样不太公平 我知道啊！
It's like I'm being punished for not having this disgusting, poisonous habit.
我不同流合污还被处罚！ 抽烟可是恶心又伤身的习惯
Yeah, it is the best.
对，抽烟最棒了
What if this keeps happening?
万一这种事没完没了怎么办？
They'll be smoking, making the decisions...
她们在外头抽烟做决定
...and I'll be up in my office breathing in my stupid clean air.
我只能在办公室里 呼吸愚蠢的新鲜空气
And when Kim wants to promote one of us...
到时等阿金要升我们的职
...who do you think she'll pick? Me or Smokey Smokerson?
你们想她会选谁？ 是我还是乌烟瘴气的冒烟女？
We used to have a smoking area at work.
我们以前的公司有抽烟区
It was great. There was this big flowerpot with dirt in it.
很棒的喔 有个小花盆，里头有土
We used to put our cigarettes out in it.
把烟放进去捻熄就行了
One of the old-timers told me there used to be a little tree in there.
公司有个元老告诉我 以前里头还有棵小树呢
You can go down there and not smoke. Say you want some fresh air.
瑞秋，你也可以一起去 不用抽烟，就说要去透透气
I could do that.
对，这是方法
Or you could do the easy thing and smoke.
简单点的就是一起抽烟
You gotta take long, deep drags.
深深吸它个一口
Wow,I still don't have my lung capacity back yet.
我的肺活量还没恢复
Rach, do you wanna go get coffee?
瑞秋，要去喝咖啡吗？
-I would love to. -Oh,good.
乐意之至 好
I'm gonna go too.
宝贝，我也想一起去
Oh,good.
好啊
Oh,I changed my mind.
等等，我变卦了
Let's talk about the party. I have so many ideas.
好，来讨论派对的事 我有一大堆点子
Me too!
我也是
Oh,look at that.
真是壮观
This is a little sketch of the cake. See?
好，这是蛋糕的素描图
Some sample menus.
还有一些菜单的样本
I thought we'd start with a Tuscan-style finger food.
不如用异国小点心当前菜
And for music, here's an alphabetized list of all of my CDs.
至于音乐呢 这是我CD收藏的字母列表
I've highlighted the ones that'll go with the food.
跟食物超搭配的还做了记号
-What about the intimate dinner party? -We're not doing that.
不是说要亲密的晚餐派对吗？ 现在不那样做了
Looks like you took care of everything. Thanks a lot,cohost.
看来你全包办了，多谢 “共同”主办人
Wait a minute. There's plenty of things for you to do.
怎么了？我没有一手包办啊 你要做的事还有很多
Like what?
举个例子？
Cups.
杯子
You're giving me cups?
杯子？你让我准备杯子？
And ice.
还有冰块
Cups and ice? I get to be in charge of cups and ice?
杯子和冰块？ 我可以负责杯子和冰块？
All right.
好吧…
Fine. I will be in charge of cups and ice.
行，我就来负责杯子和冰块
-I can get ice at the restaurant -I got it!
等等，冰块可以从餐厅拿… 冰块是我的！…
-How did the audition go? -Not so good.
试镜顺利吗？ 不太顺利
Wait a minute. Are you doing Joey's:
慢着，你在学乔伊那招吗？
"The audition didn't go so well.... Yeah,it did"?
“试镜不太顺利” 事实上很顺利！对吧？
Yeah,I am!
没错！
-Yeah,Ben got a second audition. -That's great!
班取得了第二次试镜的资格 太棒了
I had to teach Ross my bit because I actually didn't get a callback.
我得教导罗斯我的戏份 因为我没有过关
You got a callback too, didn't you?
你也过关了，对吧？
Yeah,I did!
没错！
What are you doing out here?
瑞秋，你怎么会来这里？
It got kind of lonely up there, so I thought I would come out here...
里头有点无聊 我想说来这里...
...and get some fresh air.
...透透气
We're discussing the fall collection.
南茜和我正好讨论到秋装
Oh,great.
太好了
Anyway,we really
所以这是要…
-Sorry. We're smoking all over you. -That's okay.
抱歉，瞧你被我们熏的 不好意思 没关系
We'll move. You stay there.
不成…你待着，我们走
I sent the designs to Ralph. He was excited about it.
反正我把设计寄给拉夫 他对衬里很中意
That's great! You are the best!
太好了，你是最棒的
Excuse me. Can I bum one of those?
不好意思，能给支烟吗？
Actually, this one's....
这支就好…
What's so funny over here?
你们在聊什么好笑的？
I thought you didn't smoke.
我还以为你不抽烟的
You know,I thought you guys meant marijuana cigarettes.
我以为你们是说大麻烟
You know what I mean? Doobies?
像是天使尘那种
Actually,I thought to myself, "Those guys are crazy!"
我还纳闷你们是疯了不成
But no,I smoke the regular ones all the time.
没啦，我自己也抽烟 照三餐天天都抽
We get high.
我们是在抽大麻
Me too.
我也是
I'm kidding.
闹你的
Me too.
我也是
Oh,God! This is so nerve-racking. How do you do this?
老天，这真是折磨人 你是怎么习惯的？
Fortunately,I don't get many callbacks, so....
我过关的经验不多，所以…
Is it a good sign that they asked us to wait?
我们在试镜之后被留下来 这是好现象吗？
Who knows?
天知道
We have narrowed it down to Raymond, Ben, Kyle...
最后入围的是雷蒙、班 凯尔...
...and Joey. The rest of you,thank you.
和乔伊 其余的人，辛苦了，谢谢
Yes! I knew it!
好耶，我就知道！
Bye-bye.
再会
So long.
别过
Later.
后会有期
I'm not married to him anymore. He's my ex-husband. I'm totally gay!
我不是他老婆喔，他是我前夫 我百分之百是女同志
This is great! I might get to play Ben's dad.
太棒了 我有可能饰演班的爸爸
Actually,that can't happen.
其实那是不可能的
Because you have such different looks...
因为你们各自的长相都不同
...we're putting you with Raymond and Kyle with Ben.
所以我们把你和雷蒙配对 凯尔和班是一组
So it'll either be you two or you two.
所以最后只有一组会出线
-This is gonna be kind of weird. -Yeah,it is.
要命，这样就有点尴尬了 真的是
Yeah. It's gonna be weird.
对，一定会很尴尬
No. We're like best friends. That's why it's weird.
因为我们是最好的朋友 所以才会尴尬
I thought we were just talking.
原来如此…我只是答腔而已
If Ben gets this commercial, do you think you can get me some free soup?
如果班拿到广告演出机会 你能帮我弄些免费的汤吗？
Chandler, a can of soup is like 60 cents.
钱德，一罐汤又不用多少钱
Yeah, okay,but I have been supporting a 29-year-old ltalian for five years.
对，但是我这五年来 都在供养这29岁的意大利人
Is it okay if I leave this here till Rachel's birthday party?
我能把这些东西放这里 等着给瑞秋过生日吗？
-Sure. What's in them? -Cups.
当然可以，里头是什么？ 杯子
Good, because we got Rachel 800 gallons of water.
那好，因为我们替瑞秋 准备了八百加仑的水
That's a lot of cups.
老实说，这些杯子还真不少
I'm in charge of cups and ice.
对，这是因为我负责杯子和冰块
And Monica's gonna rue the day she put me in charge of cups and ice.
摩妮卡在这一天将后悔莫及 因为她要我负责杯子和冰块
You know,I rued the day once. Didn't get a whole lot else done.
我也后悔过一次 除了后悔没做别的
Okay, time to bring up the rest of the cups.
好吧，该把其他杯子搬上来了
乔伊 菲比
Ross, I'm glad you're here.
罗斯，你在这里正好
-I want to talk to you. -What's up?
我有事要跟你说 怎么了？
I've been thinking about this commercial thing. Me against Ben.
我一直在想这次拍广告的事 我和班硬碰硬
The two of us competing. That can't lead to anything good.
捉对厮杀 这样横竖都不会有好结果
I think I'm just gonna step aside. I'll tell them that I won't audition.
我想我还是退出好了 告诉他们我不去试镜
Joey, that's great. Thanks,man.
乔伊，太好了，多谢
That's it?
就这样？
You're gonna let me do this? It's my career we're talking about!
你真要让我这样做？ 这事关我的职业生涯耶
But you just
可是你说…
I just said that so you wouldn't let Ben do it.
我是要套你说出让班退出
If anyone should step aside, it should be Ben.
罗斯，如果真有人要退出 那也应该是班
-What? -Chandler,tell him!
什么？ 钱德，告诉他为什么
Well, let me get the door first.
我先去开门
Hi,no one!
没有人，你好
Why should Ben step aside?
班为什么应该退出？
It was his audition in the first place. You tagged along.
这原本就是他的试镜 你是跟过去的
You're like the tagalong dad!
就像是跟班老爹
At least I care about his feelings.
起码我有顾虑到班的感受
What?
什么？
You know how hard it'll be on him when he doesn't get it?
你知道万一他没通过试镜 到时他会有多难过吗？
And why wouldn't he get it?
那他又为什么不会通过？
Come on!
得了吧？
Have you seen what my kid can do?
你有没有看过 跟我同组的小子有多厉害？
He dials phones, he eats tortilla chips.
他会拨电话、吃墨西哥脆片
He plays soccer with the cartoon tiger!
还会凭空踢足球演对手戏呢
Are you saying your kid eats soup better than my kid?
你是说你的小子喝汤 比我儿子厉害？
You just give him a spoon,baby.
你儿子才刚学会喝汤呢
Oh,yeah? I guess we'll see!
是吗？我们走着瞧
This commercial belongs to me and Mitch!
好啊，这支广告片的主角 非我和米契莫属
-Your kid's name is Raymond! -Yeah? So is yours!
你的孩子叫做雷蒙 对，你的也是！
（中央咖啡馆）
-How did work go? -lt was great.
有没有用？ 很棒…
I went down there like you said. And we talked business.
我听你们的建议 去她们抽烟的地方 我们讨论到了生意
And Kim took my opinions.
阿金完全接受我的意见
You stink!
你浑身烟味
-Thanks. -No,I'm serious.
多谢 我是说真的
That's because I went down there and they were smoking.
因为那里的人全都在抽烟
This is actually the smell of success.
这其实是成功的味道
But there's something different
不过有点怪怪的
Oh,my God! You smoked!
天啊，你有抽烟
I did not.
我没有
Yes, you did. You look happy and sick. You smoked!
才怪，你看起来生病又快乐 你一定有抽烟
All right, fine! But I had to. I had to do it for my career.
好啦…我有抽 为了事业不得已
I wish I had to smoke for my career.
好羡慕
But it's so gross!
这样很恶心耶
It's not that bad, you know?
没那么糟啦
Yeah,my tongue feels a little fuzzy and my fingers sort of smell.
虽然舌头有点打结 手指也有点怪味
I actually feel like I could throw up.
其实我感觉快吐了
-Can you hear yourself? -I know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
听你自己在说什么 我知道…我也很后悔
I'm not myself. I smoked like half a pack.
我都不是我自己了 我抽了半包烟
I feel a little shaky and a little weird.
感觉怪怪的，还在发抖
But you gotta push past this, okay? Because it's about to get so good.
好，但你一定要撑过这一关 再来就会是快乐无比了
钱德
You smell so smoky, I gotta get up.
你浑身烟味，我得去透透气
I'm not kidding.
我没骗你
I think you smell great.
我觉得你闻起来很香
So we're decided. No on plaid, yes on pink.
所以大家都同意了 不要格子图案，要粉红？
Absolutely.
完全正确
I'm so onboard.
我举双手双脚赞成
-Didn't you just light that? -Yeah.
瑞秋，这支烟不是才刚点？ 是啊
But you know what?
但是...
I'm just really,really trying to cut back, you know.
我正在努力少抽烟
Good luck, Rach.
“瑞秋，我等着看笑话”
I've been thinking about quitting.
其实我最近有想要戒烟
Every Sunday night, I tell myself I'm quitting.
那可不，我每周日晚上 都告诉自己要戒烟
Every Monday morning, it's like:
结果周一还不是狂抽猛抽
Tell me about it.
还用你说
We'll just quit. Let's all quit!
那就戒了吧，我们一起戒烟
It sounds appealing.
听起来是很诱人啦
-I never could do it. -But you could. Absolutely.
我戒烟从没成功过 你可以的，一定行
We can help each other. We could get those patches.
我们可以互相帮忙 用那个什么戒烟贴布的
We could be like the Patch Sisters.
我们能组成戒烟三姐妹
You know,we really should quit. Okay, let's quit!
其实我们真的应该戒烟 好吧，一起来戒烟
Great! Give me those cigs. Come on!
太棒了，把香烟给我 来
Give it! Out. Done. Quit.
通通交出来
My late husband gave me that lighter.
那个打火机是我先夫送我的
I'm not kidding.
我没在开玩笑
Okay,then.
那好吧
Mmm...soup.
汤
Joey, Ross is gonna be here any second, would you mind watching Ben for me while I use the ladies' room?
乔伊，罗斯随时会到 我去上个厕所 帮我看一下班，好吗？
-No problem. -Thanks.
好啊，没问题 谢谢
嗨，班
So you want to be an actor? I gotta tell you, it's no picnic.
你想当演员啊？ 告诉你，演戏可不像野餐
There's tons of rejection. No stability.
有碰不完的钉子 一点都不稳定
I mean,one day, you're Dr. Drake Ramoray.
前一天你还是德瑞克医生
The next day,you're eating ketchup out of the bottle.
隔天你就要去啃番茄酱
It's a tough life. I mean, sure, you can get up whenever you want...
这可是艰苦的生活 没错啦，你是能决定起床时间
...watch TV all day...
整天看电视也行
...meet tons of women in acting class....
在演员训练班里 认识一卡车的女孩
Oh, who am I kidding. I can't talk you out of this. It's a great life.
小子，我干嘛劝你打消念头 这种生活太棒了
-Joey. -Ross.
乔伊 罗斯
Ben.
班
I mean,Ben. Ben.
班…
Raymond, Joey, you're up.
雷蒙，乔伊，该你们上场了
So here's what....
好，现在要…
Are you sure that I haven't seen you somewhere before?
我一定有在哪里见过你
No, I haven't been in any plays.
没有，我都待在家
All right,let's try one. Whenever you guys are ready.
好吧，我们来试一次 你们准备好了就开始
Is there a problem?
有问题吗？
Well,this is noodle soup. And I've been working with tomato.
这是面汤 我练习时是用番茄汤
But that's okay. No problem.
不过没关系…
Mmm...noodle soup.
面汤…
You know,that's fine. But the line is,"Mmm...soup."
你那样不错 不过台词是“汤”
-What'd I say? -"Mmm...noodle soup."
那我刚才说什么？ “面汤”
How's that different?
有什么不一样？
对…
All right. Let's try one.
好，我们来试一次
Mmm...
...noodle soup.
面汤
Let's do it again.
好，我们再来一次
Mmm...soup.
汤
I mean, noodle soup. I mean, soup!
我是说“面汤” 不对，是“汤”
Come on!
你争气点
You know what? We need to move on.
我们得换下一组了
No,I could do it one more time.
不…我再演一次
Look.
你看
Mmm...noodle soup.
面汤…
Damn it!
可恶！
So I think that if we get these samples into the magazine by Monday,we'll be fine.
周一前把样品交给杂志社 应该就没问题了
Sounds good. So, Rach, how you doing?
听起来不错  瑞秋，你还好吗？
-I'm great! -No, with the not-smoking thing.
好极了 不，我是说戒烟的事
Kill me now.
可把我给搞死了
Let me tell you something, I ate 40 Mallomars today.
跟你说 我今天吃了40个棉花糖
I mean, I have patches all over my body, you know?
全身贴满了戒烟贴布
-I mean,I haven't slept in two days. -We quit yesterday.
我连续两天都失眠 我们昨天才戒烟的
That's counting today.
我连今天都算进去了
But anyway, so these samples,I think
言归正传，我想这些样品…
Oh,my God!
天啊
I'm so sorry, I forgot. I have to go to the mailroom and mail some proofs.
我忘记了，真的很抱歉 我得去收发室寄送样张
Go ahead. Rachel and I will just sit here and keep brainstorming.
尽管去 我和瑞秋继续来脑力激荡
Also,Vogue called. And they were wondering
时尚杂志也想知道… 你知道吗？…
You know what? I'm a little hungry. I'm just gonna run down to the vending machines.
我有点饿了 我要去贩卖机买东西
All right.
好吧
Busted!
被逮到了
Come on! What are you doing? I thought we were the Patch Sisters.
你们这是在干嘛？ 我们不是戒烟姐妹花吗？
That didn't work out.
对，那样行不通
Wait a minute. What about all we've talked about?
那我们说过的那些事呢？
You know,the disgusting place, the ugly people.
说这恶心的地方，丑陋的人
Hey,how you doing?
你好吗？
We tried to quit. But it was too hard.
瑞秋，我们有试着戒烟 但那实在是太难了
If you started smoking again, you could have at least told me.
你们开始抽烟 起码也该告诉我嘛
Give me one of those. What are we talking about?
快点来一支，刚才说到哪里？
No! You're doing great! Don't you give up.
不行，你戒烟很成功 不许放弃
That's why we didn't tell you, and we won't drag you down.
所以我们才没跟你说 我们不想拖你下水
Wait. No,no. Drag me down.
等等，别这样，拖我下水…
Forget it. We're so proud of how well you're doing.
瑞秋，万万不可 你戒烟成功，我们都替你骄傲
I won't let you blow it. If I catch you, you're fired.
我不能让你前功尽弃 若被我捉到 我一定炒你鱿鱼
Go on,get out of here. I don't want you breathing this stuff.
走吧，离开这里 我不要你吸二手烟
So, okay. You'll come with me on the Paris trip?
好，你和我一起去法国出差
Oh,man!
要命！
Check it out. Cup hat, cup banner...
你瞧瞧，杯子帽 杯子布条
...cup chandelier, and the thing that started it all: the cup!
杯子吊灯  还有本尊：杯子
Great job with the cups.
菲比，你对杯子还真有一套
Why don't you just go out with her?
你干脆跟她去约会算了
Did you notice the ice? Look!
你有没有注意到冰？
We have it all. We have crushed, cubed and dry. Watch.
各式各样的都有 有碎冰、冰块 还有干冰 注意看
Mystical.
很有神秘感吧？
Everyone-no one's eating my Tuscan finger food. Because they're all filling up on Phoebe's snow cones!
没人想吃我的小点心 他们全跑去吃菲比的雪花冰
There are snow cones?
有雪花冰？
Snow cones! Yuck!
雪花冰最恶心了！
-Go,go! Right there! -Thank you.
你去吃啦 谢谢…
菲比？
-You really did do a nice job. -Thank you...
你做的很棒 谢谢你
...for stating the obvious.
看就知道
I deserve that.
我活该
I just want you to know that if we ever cohost a party together again...
我只是要让你知道 若我们下回再一起主办派对
-...you can do whatever you want. -Joey's got a birthday coming up.
你想要怎么做都行 乔伊的生日快到了
-Really? What do you wanna do? -Okay,I'd like to be in charge of beer.
真的？ 那你要怎么帮他庆祝？ 好，我想要负责啤酒
Well,then there's nothing left for me.
那我就没的做了
-Look,look! -Surprise!
注意！… 惊喜！
What? My birthday is not for another month.
什么啊？ 一个月后才是我生日啊
That's the surprise.
这样才惊喜啊
Oh,my God, you guys! This is so great! It's so unexpected.
天啊，你们太棒了 我完全没想到
I mean,Chandler's birthday is even before mine.
钱德的生日还比我早到呢
Surprise!
惊喜！
This is so great! Look at all these...
真是太棒了，看看这些...
...cups.
...杯子
This is so weird.
真是怪怪的
I was in charge of cups.
杯子是我负责的
Oh,okay. Not so weird.
好，那就没那么怪了
-Chandler, what are you doing? -Nothing.
钱德，你在干嘛？ 没干嘛
-What's in your hand? -Money. I'm stealing all the money.
你手里拿是什么？ 钱，我偷走了所有的钱
Chandler.
钱德
But just one, okay? Because nobody knows when my birthday is.
抽一支就好 因为没有人记得我的生日
Let me make this clear to you,okay?
或许这能让你清醒一点
It's either that...
有香烟…
...or this.
就没有我
They were menthol.
刚才那是薄荷烟
Listen, man. I'm sorry the audition didn't go well.
我很遗憾你试镜不顺利
Yeah, right.
是喔
No, really. I am, Joey. I feel bad.
乔伊，我是真的很遗憾
Look, Ross. You don't have to,okay?
罗斯，你用不着遗憾
It's not your fault I suck.
是我自己逊，怨不得你
What kind of an actor can't even say, "Mmm...noodle soup"?
连“面汤”都说不好 还算哪门子的演员？
You know what? Maybe you didn't mess up your audition because you suck.
你知道吗？或许你搞砸了试镜 不是因为你逊
Maybe you messed up because you care more about your godson.
或许你搞砸了试镜 是因为你更在意你的教子
What do you mean?
什么意思？
I think, subconsciously
我认为，在潜意识里…
You lost me.
等等，我听不懂
I think,on some level, you sabotaged...
我觉得在某种程度上 你破坏了....
...your own audition so Ben would get the part.
自己的试镜 才好让班拿到那个角色
Your way sounds a lot better than mine.
你的说法比我的好多了
It's not that I'm a bad actor.
对，不是我演技烂
No,it's just that I care so damn much about little Ben...
对 只是我考虑的都是班
...that it was more important for me to see him succeed.
看到他成功对我来说更重要
-There you go. Thank you. -Thank you.
就是这样，谢谢你 谢谢你
-So did he get it? -No.
那他拿到角色没？ 没有
What are you gonna do?
不如意事十之八九嘛
Excuse me, is Rachel Green here? I'm meeting her for lunch.
不好意思，瑞秋葛林在吗？ 我跟她约了吃中饭
She doesn't come down anymore. You can find her up on 10.
她现在不会下来这里了 她在十楼
Okay,great.
好…
So we talked about the presentation.
我们昨天中饭聊到提案报告
He wondered if one person would be enough.
他担心一个人出差不够看
And I said, "Yeah,absolutely."
我说绝对没问题
I'll catch you guys later.
后会有期了